emotions when you got the call and was
it a surprise where the call came from
or did you have a feeling that uh
Baltimore might be the place?
>> Uh I I had a feeling that that Baltimore
could be the place. Um and I mean the
emotions was just is overwhelming just a
surreal moment. Um, you know, the the
Ravens, they traded up for it, so like
it it was a little bit of a surprise
just the timing of it all, but um, I
mean, just an overwhelming feeling of of
being incredibly blessed and and just
ready to to make the most of it.
>> Go to Cliff Brown.
>> Yeah, man. Congratulations. Uh,
>> thank you. Can can you talk about why
you had an inkling about Baltimore and
also your thoughts about uh being in
offense with Lamar Jackson, Derek Henry,
etc.?
>> Yeah. Um well, I I went to the Ravens
local proday. Um had a really great
time. Met, you know, spent time with
Coach Graci, spent time with with Coach
Doyle, met with Coach Menor as well. Um
actually, Coach Graci texted me before
uh before today's uh draft started and
just said good luck with the draft and
everything. and and so, you know, I
mean, obviously there's a lot of
uncertainty, but uh you know, there's a
little bit of an inkling that that kind
of made me excited. Um, but you know,
just the idea of being able to go join a
team full of of so many weapons and
Lamar Jackson, Derrick Henry, I mean,
Mark Andrews, like being able to to be
in such a powerful, you know, explosive
offense and and try to learn from from,
you know, veterans in the room and and
just take what I can and just be a
sponge my first year. Um, I I really
can't think of a better fit, honestly.
I'm just I'm so looking forward to it. I
can't wait.
>> Let's go to Brian Wacker, please. And
then Gianna Han.
>> Hey, Matt. Congrats. Thanks for doing
this. Um, obviously you were at
Michigan, I think, when Jesse Min was
there. Just your familiarity with him
and sort of how you see yourself, um,
you know, on a Jesse Mentor coach team
and within this offense from what you
know.
>> Yeah, I mean, yeah, it was it was it was
cool. when I met with coach Menor, we
kind of were able to chat about like
both of our times at Michigan and just
have that like pre-established
relationship which is great. I mean that
was a really close-knit team. Um but I
think you know just doing whatever I can
uh you know on and off the field like
embracing special teams like that's
going to be a big role for me while I
was at Michigan that was you know a
major that's how I got on the field and
made the most impact. Um, and then being
a part of the Ravens offense, you know,
kind of fitting into the zone schemes,
being um, you know, able to kind of be a
plugand play, be able to be versatile
and and really do whatever they need
from a blocking standpoint and a passing
standpoint.
>> Just building off of that, um, I was
wondering, you know, the Ravens lost a
lot in their tight endings in free
agency with Isaiah likely Charlie Kohler
and they had Mark Andrew left. I guess
how do you see yourself fitting into
what they have and um like where would
you say your specialty is at?
>> Yeah. Um I think I mean if I were I
would kind of see myself as more of like
that Isaiah likely type of fit. Um I
actually you know I know Charlie Kohler
so so shout out to him. He's trained at
the same place that that I've trained
at. Um and he's an awesome dude. But uh
um you know I think you know being able
to play in line is is important but also
you know being able to get downfield be
able to make plays and you know be
consistent pass catcher as well.
>> Go to Kyle Goon and then Jeff Zerbeck.
>> Yeah Matt, welcome to Baltimore. Um, you
know, do you feel like there are aspects
of your game or skills that you have or
potential that you have that you were
not able to show in college that might
translate at the NFL level?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think obviously there
there's always work to be done. I think
that's, you know, a benefit is like I I
can see things looking back on film that
that I can improve and get better at. my
hand placement, you know, being able to
punch, uh, being heavierhanded and and
my footwork and really running off the
ball at times. Um, just, you know, even
even with meeting with coach Gracie,
kind of talking about some of those
things and where I can improve and and
kind of how I'm going to, you know, be
playing plan to do that. Um, but but,
you know, that's kind of the nice thing
about it is like knowing there's still
more potential. And I think, um, I'm
sorry, I'm getting a call from Coach
Gracie. Am I still
I gotta am my back on this.
>> Yeah, you're back.
>> Okay, awesome. Um, I'm gonna go ahead
and shoot him a text real quick if
that's okay.
Um, I'm sorry, but but I think, you
know, there's always, you know, you
always feel like there's meat on the
bone, like in and all my college
seasons, you know, and I think, you
know, that just having that mentality of
like knowing that I can always do more
um and working to do that and and
finding ways to develop and and being
able to establish that. I mean, part of
that's, you know, just opportunity and
part of that's like, you know, earning
that opportunity. So, I think it's it's
kind of a mix, but I'm looking forward
to to making the most and embracing the,
you know, developing and being able to
to capitalize on more and more.
>> Let's close it out with Jeff so he can
get back to coach, please.
>> Matthew, who are sort of the tight ends
that you've looked up to or emulated or
you sort of patterned your game after?
>> Yeah, I mean, through college, uh, I I
really I enjoyed watching Dallas GD. Um,
he was kind of someone who I emulated a
bit just with his body type, the way
that he plays. Um, you know, I I' I've
been with a lot of tight ends who are
playing at a high level now. Like I
played with Coulson Loveland, Luke
Skoomaker. Uh, love watching them play,
good friends of mine. Um, and uh, you
know, Mark Andrews has been around
forever. I've watched him for as long as
I can remember. So, you know, watching
him and his production, I mean, the
amount of receptions and and yards he's
able to get and still, you know, the way
he produces in the run game, it's it's
incredible and his longevity. So,
hopefully I I can pick his brain a
little bit and and learn from him. But
yeah, those are those are some of the
the models that I've kind of tried to
model my game after.
>> All right, Matt, thank you so much for
joining us today. We appreciate it.
Congratulations on being drafted by the
Ravens, and we're looking forward to
meeting you here in person soon.
>> Yes, sir. Me, too. Likewise. Thank you
so much. Christian.